Víctor O. Meza Márquez Centro Candoral, Torre B, Piso 14, Apto. 145-B – La Candelaria

Caracas – Dtto. Capital - Venezuela Phone: +58 416.362.7525/+58 412.980.6740

e-mail: vmezamarquez@gmail.com

SUMARY

Bachelor of Business Administration and Computer Science and active training in the area of Health Sciences with experience in planning, organization and execution of administrative and instructional processes. Easy to establish effective interpersonal relationships, ease of oral, written and graphic in English and Spanish. Ability to work under pressure, numerical and analytical capacity oriented problem solving, achievement and teamwork.

REMOTE WORK EXPERIENCE

1. - RPLANTS (Ornamental Plants) located in Homestead, Florida.

As a Team Manager, I supervised the following activities:

Checking all the sales orders received by emails from the sales team.

Assigning the sales orders to the operators to upload them into the CRM system.

Checking the process of completing the sales orders in the farms.

Solving situations with the technical equipment (telephone sets, tablets, printers & internet connections) in the farms.

2. - MY RENTAL AGENT - (Real Estate) located in Hialeah, Florida.

As a Team Manager, I supervised the following activities:

Manage client/owner emails and their calendar.

Set-up automatic bookings online and share booking links with lead/clients as needed.

Help leads book calls with real estate agents manually or using booking systems like

Calendly. Review the calendar and find out about availability to set calls or appointments with team leaders.

Send a calendar invite to both realtors and leads/clients.

Set appointments with corporate/investment banking and capital investors for introductions in real estate and other fields.

Set calls/appointments with acquisition experts.

Update all dates and pertinent information into software custom fields like FUB.

3. - THE OWNER APP - (Real Estate) located in Hialeah, Florida.

As a Team Manager, I supervised the following activities:

Cold call contacts gathered by lead generation or research.

Calling distressed owners or people that may want to sell their house.

Calling people interested in buying/selling their house.

Adding call notes to a CRM system (as needed), and/or assigning hot/interested leads to another team member for additional sales follow-up.

Calling the owners of the houses offering to buy them if the house has the potential to be sold.

Pre-screening new potential clients, and making sure they're the right fit to be clients.

Speaking to people over the phone and turning leads into clients.

Outbound calling, e-mail communication, coordination and scheduling of real estate buying and selling opportunities and overall management of sales pipeline. Helping with upselling additional services to existing clients.

Follow-up with existing clients to gather feedback and/or reviews.

Receiving and tracking emails for new real estate deals in the company's pipeline (buyers or sellers pipeline).

4. - ENGLISH SPOT - (English Academy) located in Doral, Florida.

As a Team Manager, I supervised the following activities:

Calling potential leads over the phone and offering info about the courses the company offers.

Performing outbound calls to past clients or existing leads the company already has.

Speaking with each lead, take notes, and then add them to the CRM.

Calling leads and prospects to book demos and/or introductory calls manually or through online booking systems.

Inviting clients to events and asking for referrals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administradora Grupo Pronto S.A.

2012-2016

Third-party Administration Company for organizations with self-insured plans, and technological services for insurance companies wishing to outsource the management of their plans.

Position: Claim Team Manager.

Activities and Responsibilities: Plan, organize and direct a medical claims unit. Monitor billing activities, performance management, production standards and quality of results. Provide technical assistance to supervisory staff to initiate billing to all appropriate payer types. Analyze data for bill presentation based on technical and compliance requirements and review claims for quality and compliance. Support the technical application of systems such as billing modalities, benefit plans and systems set up and review and interpret the impact of new applications or updates. Evaluate statistical reports to monitor revenue production for management and identify potential issues and controls for use in training and development. Review accounts receivable including unapplied payment allocation and/or other transactions to ensure accuracy. Prepare, or supervise the preparation of, and analyze pre-billing and pre-closing processes and bill presentation to ensure quality, accuracy, and compliance with regulations. Staying informed and implement changes in regulations regarding billing requirements. Coordinate, maintain liaisons with, and provide feedback to other divisions, departments, and agencies to resolve problems or discrepancies in processing claims and billing. Provide technical help desk support as needed and identify trends for potential training and development of staff, programs, and

management. Provide responsive, high quality service to employees, representatives of outside agencies, and members of the public by providing accurate, complete, and up-to-date information, in a courteous, efficient, and timely manner.

Gerencia Médica Integral (GMI GROUP)

2004-2011

Third-party Administration Company and Primary Health Care Center.

Position: Primary Health Care Manager

Activities and Responsibilities: Providing overall direction and management for the service, facility and the organization of the center. Developing, implementing and monitoring procedures, policies and standards for medical, nursing, allied health and administrative staff. Coordinating and administering health and welfare programs and clinical services. Monitoring and evaluating resources devoted to health, welfare, recreation, housing, employment, training and other community facilities. Controlling administrative operations such as budget planning, report preparation, expenditure on supplies, equipment and services. Liaising with other health and welfare providers, boards and funding bodies to discuss areas of health and welfare service cooperation and coordination. Advising government bodies about measures to improve health and welfare services and facilities. Representing the organization in negotiations, and at conventions, seminars, public hearings and forums. Controlling selection, training and supervision of staff.

C.A. de Seguros American International

1998-2003

Insurance Company.

Position: Gerente de Responsabilidad Civil y Patronal.

Activities and Responsibilities: Process applications, policies, endorsements, binders, certificates, audit requests and other items related to the servicing of clients. Assist clients with policy coverage, exclusions and related questions and assist Producers in servicing clients. Service client accounts with oversight of Producers or Account Executives, which includes research/analysis and handling of client questions on coverage and other policy/contractual issues. Make routine policy adjustments. Conduct renewal process with oversight of Producers or Account Executives, including exposure analysis for client (e.g., review census/experience data, contractual requirements for insurance), strategize with Producer/Account Executive and client regarding whether to market and if applicable, conduct market comparisons by analyzing insurance rate and renewal information, obtain and evaluate quotes, negotiate premium and commission rates on behalf of clients for best alternatives, prepare proposal, and oversees accuracy of insurance binder. Provide support to Producers and, if applicable, Account Executives, including preparing presentations and proposals, and participating in meetings with prospective clients as part of team. Prepare billing and provide standard office/administrative support.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration and Computer Science

1995

Universidad Nacional Experimental Simón Rodríguez

TRAINING COURSES

Medical Services (Public & Private Health System) I & II. Coverage of Healthcare System.

Business Processes Reengineering.
Planning, Problem Analysis & Decision-making.
Statistic Applied to Insurance.
Fostering Microenterprise Level I.
Fostering Microenterprise Level II.
Accounting Standards for Productive Communities.
Marketing and Sales Program.
Customer Image & Service.
Communication and Influencing Skills.

PERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork, Creativity, Adaptability, Leadership, Trust, Success orientation, Technical knowledge, Reliability and Catalyst for change